# Zachary Bohn Developer and Designer

## **Professional Summary**

I am a meticulous developer and designer, focused on design and development of impactful user experiences. I am currently a Creative Technology and Design masters student, where I am concentrating on web development, user experience design, and creative technologies. Previously, I worked in product strategy and marketing research and cofounded Helena.org. To see my work please visit www.zacharybohn.com.

### **Experience**

#### **Seminaut Game Studios**

Oct 2022 - Present

### Web Development and UX Intern

• Front-end development and design of a platform to facilitate social gaming (starts Oct 19th)

#### **ZS** Associates

Nov 2020 - Jan 2022

### Strategy, Insights, and Planning Associate

- Completed ten projects helping companies with marketing research and product strategy, including:
  - Defined customer personas based on distinct characteristics and created messaging that resonated with each persona, resulting in successful launch

#### Simon-Kucher and Partners

Nov 2019 - Nov 2022

### Consultant (Oct-Jun) | Innovation Associate (Jun-Oct)

- UX research, prototyping, and business case development for internal start-up, leading to successful launch
- Co-founded social impact group with 20 members

#### Parakeet Health

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

#### Chief Executive Officer and UX Designer

- Led team of 5 to create high-fidelity prototype design activities included personas, customer journey map, wireframes, brand guidelines, and high-fi mock-ups
- Business pitch and prototype placed first in USC Health Systema Innovation Collaborative Challenge, a \$10K entrepreneurship competition

### Helena.org

Apr 2015 - Mar 2017

#### Cofounder

- · Created and validated concept through user interviews, recruited members, developed brand, and created fundraising documents, resulting in more than \$21M raised to date
- Helena.org has moved more than 37 million pieces of PPE to hospitals and health workers to help with COVID-19

### **Contact Information**

Portfolio: www.zacharybohn.com Email: zacharybohn1@gmail.com

**LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/zacharymbohn

### **Skills**

### **Development**

HTML5 & CSS3

**JavaScript** 

React

Responsive UI

SASS

Three.js

P5.js

SQL(some)

Python(some)

Flask(some)

### Design

Figma

Sketch

Rapid Prototyping

Interaction Design

**UX** Research

### **Education**

### **University of Colorado at Boulder** M.S. Creative Technology and Design

2022 - 2024 | GPA: TBD

Graduate Courses (First Year): Creative Coding, Front-End Development II, Design Methods, UX Design, Design Studio, Programming and Data Structures, CSS for Javascript Developers

### **University of Southern California B.S.** Business Administration 2019 | GPA: 3.6

Honors: Global Student Entrepreneurship Award, Lime Fellow, USC Continuing Student Scholarship, Cum Laude

### **Supplemental Education**

**Harvard Extension** Intensive Introduction to Computer Science 2022 | GPA: 4.0

The App Brewery The Complete Web Development Bootcamp 2022